Guide to the Stephanie Spangler, Deputy Provost for Biomedical and Health Affairs, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Stephanie Spangler, deputy provost for biomedical and health affairs, Yale University, records
1986-2007
RU 1057
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
14
(14 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, committee and planning documents, and project and procedure files maintained by Dr. Stephanie Spangler as deputy provost for biomedical and health affairs at Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Spangler, Stephanie
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Provost's Office, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, committee and planning documents, and project and procedure files maintained by Dr. Stephanie Spangler as deputy provost for biomedical and health affairs at Yale University.
Biomedicine -- Administration; Science -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Deputy provost Stephanie Spangler records, 1986-2007; Accession 2008-A-013
  Conditions Governing Access
  The records are closed until 35 years from the end of the tenure of Deputy Provost Stephanie Spangler due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
  - Academic Health Centers, 1995 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action OFCCP Audit, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action Director Search, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Experimental Station, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alliance, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AMA, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Americares, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Animal Assurance, VA, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Animal Care Assurance, 1995- 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Animal Care Assurance, 2002 -2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Animal Care, 1987- 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Administration Budget, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Administration Budget Capital Budget, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Administration Budget Director Search, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Agency Accounts, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Animal Care Executive Committee, 1999- 2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Budget Operating
    - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Budget Planning, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25 - 27)
  - BUH
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - AAHC, 1998- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - AAMC, 1997- 2001 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - AAU
    - 2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - AAU COI, 2000- 2001 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - AAU EXPERIMENTAL USE, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - AAU IP, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - ACADEMIC FRAUD CASES, 1995- 2001 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - ACADEMIC MEDICAL CENTERS, 1995- 2000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - ACHMOO CIGNA DECISION, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - ACHMO'S OTHER HMO'S, 1994- 2000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - ACEM
    - 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 46 - 49)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Green Fund Evaluation, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Administration Expense Account (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Green Fund Proposals (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Green Fund Documents (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Land Use Subcommittee, 2001- 2002 (Box 2, Folder 55 - 56)
    - Press (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Yale University Environmental (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Yale Green Fund Procedures and Approved Projects (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Green Fund Procedures and Guidelines, 2003 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - ACHMO, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - ACOG, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - AETNA, 1997- 1999 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Aids in Africa, 2001- 2002 (Box 2, Folder 64 - 65)
  - AIDS BMS, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - APT FWA, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - AYA, 1995- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - AYA YALE MEDICAL, 1995- 1996 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Bioethics Executive Committee
    - 2006 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - 2005 (Box 3, Folder 71 - 72)
  - Biological Safety Committee
    - 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - 1996 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 76 - 77)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 82 - 83)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Biosafety Sunshine Project File (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Bioethics
    - 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Bioethics Executive Committee
    - 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 90 - 91)
    - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 92 - 93)
    - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 94 - 95)
    - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 96 - 98)
    - 2004 (Box 4, Folder 99 - 100)
  - Budget Steering, 1996-2004 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Committees
    General
    Box 5, Folders 102-121 returned permanently to the Office of the Provost, 2015.
    - 1995-1997 (Box 5)
    - 1997 (Box 5)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 5)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 5)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 5)
    - 1999-2003 (Box 5)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 5)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 5)
    - 2003 (Box 5)
    - 2004 (Box 5)
  - Clintons, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - COI (Conflict of Interest)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - GAO
      - Awards w/HIC Protocol, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 125)
      - Committee on Cooperative Research Patentsand License, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 126)
      - Conflict of Interest minutes, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 127)
      - Conflict of Interest Policy, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 128)
      - Data Base Checks, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 129)
      - Disclosure Forms, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 130)
      - Disclosure Forms Update, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Guidelines for Investigators the HIC Committee (Box 6, Folder 132)
      - Financial COI Clinical Research GAO Study, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 133)
      - Financial Relationship w/Industry-Bill Summers, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 134)
      - Grant and Contracts, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 135)
      - Handwritten Notes (mostly Bobs), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - Meeting Notes Beckerton, 1996 April 18 (Box 6, Folder 137)
      - Other Support for PIS w/managed COI, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 139 - 140)
      - OCR Crosswalk, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - Protocols List, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 142)
      - OCR Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 143 - 144)
      - Statistics (GAO Grid), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 148)
      - Visit Schedule, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 149)
      - YSM Protocol Disclosure Statement (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - Yale University Faculty Handbook, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Gift Implementation and Stewardship Committee
    - 2001 Sep (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - 2001 May (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - 2001 Apr (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - 2001 Mar (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - 2001 Feb (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - 2001 Jan (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - 2000 Dec (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - 2000 Nov (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - 2000 Oct (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - 2000 Jul (Box 6, Folder 161 - 162)
    - 2000 Jun (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - 2000 May (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - 2000 Jan (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Conflict of Interest
    - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Disabilities Advisory Committee
    - 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 171 - 172)
    - 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Disabilities
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Disabilities Committee
    - 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Disabilities, 2003- 2004 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Employee Reimbursement and CK Requests
    - 2000 (Box 7, Folder 182 - 183)
    - 2001 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - 2001 (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - 2002 (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - EPH Sac Committee
    - 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - EPH
    - 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - UBC
    - 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 193)
    - 1999 (Box 8, Folder 194)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 195)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 196)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 197)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - UNIVERSITY SAFETY COMMITTEE
    - 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 199)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 200)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 201)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 202)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 203)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - YSM
    - SWIM (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - LOA, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 206)
  - YSN
    - PANORAMA
      - 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 207)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - SAAC
      - 1999 2000 (Box 8, Folder 209)
      - 2000 2001 (Box 8, Folder 210)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 211)
      - 2002 2003 (Box 8, Folder 212)
      - 2003 2004 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - YACUC ANIMAL CARE
    - 1996-97 (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - 1997-98 (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - 1998-99 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - YSM
    - Budget
      - 1993 (Box 9, Folder 219)
      - 1995 (Box 9, Folder 220)
      - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 221)
      - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 222)
      - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 223)
      - 1998 (Box 9, Folder 224)
      - 1999 (Box 9, Folder 225)
      - 2000 (Box 9, Folder 226)
      - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 227)
      - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 228)
      - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 229)
      - 2004 (Box 9, Folder 230 - 231)
    - Dean Search Committee
      - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 232)
      - 2004 (Box 9, Folder 233)
    - Faculty
    - AFFAIR, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 234)
    - APPOINTMENTS
      - 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 235)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 236 - 237)
    - COMPENSATION GUIDELINES, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 238)
    - Issues
      - 1996 2003 (Box 9, Folder 239)
      - 1996-2003 (Box 9, Folder 240)
      - 2004 2005 (Box 9, Folder 241)
      - 2004 2005 (Box 9, Folder 242)
    - FINANCE, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 243)
    - FINANCIAL PLAN, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - SURGERY CHAIR SEARCH, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - YUHS EDUCATION COMMITTEE, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - OEO
    - Candidates, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 247)
    - Candidates, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 251)
    - Referrals, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 252)
  - POST DOCS
    - 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 253)
    - 2000 (Box 10, Folder 254)
    - 2000 (Box 10, Folder 255)
    - 2000 (Box 10, Folder 256)
  - PROJECT X, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 257)
  - PROJECT S, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 258)
  - PROTECTION IN HUMAN SUBJECTS
    - 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 259)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 260)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - PROVOST EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT SEARCH, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - POSITION INFORMATION, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - INTERVIEWS W/ PROVOST and DEPUTY PROVOST, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 264)
  - INTERVIEWS W/PROVOST and ASSOC PROVOST, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 265)
  - APPLICATIONS SCREENED BY PROVOST NOT SEEN, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - RADIATION SAFETY COMMITTEE
    - 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 267)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 268)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 269)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 270)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 271)
    - 2001 2002 (Box 10, Folder 272)
    - 2002 2003 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - RESEARCH COMPLIANCE, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - SSS SPEANCHES LAMB DEPT, 2006 April (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - STRIKE, 1996 -2003 (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - FAS Teaching
    - 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 278 - 279)
    - 1995-2002 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Faculty Meetings Administration, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Faculty Orientation, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 282)
  - Grants
    - All Projects Overview Strategy Meetings, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 283)
    - Financials
      - 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 284)
      - 2005 (Box 11, Folder 285)
      - 2005 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - HR
    - M/P Salaries, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 287)
    - Spouse Program, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Staffing, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Hartigan Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - High School Students, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - HIPAA
    - 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Policies, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - History of Science and Medicine Teaching
    - 2003 (Box 11, Folder 294)
    - Blue Note book, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Human Investigation Committee
    - 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Human Subjects Committee
    - 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Human Subjects Policies, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Human Subjects Protection Pending Legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Humanities Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - IACUC
    - 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - International Education, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Office of Environmental and Health Safety (OEHS)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 308)
    - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 309)
    - 1998 (Box 12, Folder 310)
    - 1999 (Box 12, Folder 311)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 313)
    - 2004 (Box 12, Folder 314)
    - Animal Report, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Animal Care, 1996-2002 (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Asbestos, 1996- 1998 (Box 12, Folder 317)
    - Asbestos Leak, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 318)
    - Audit, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 319)
    - BL3 Legislation, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 320)
    - Badge Incident, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 321)
    - Barnwell, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Biomedical Waste, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 324)
    - Biosafety, 1999-2004 (Box 12, Folder 325)
    - Biosafety CDC, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 326)
    - Biosafety, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 327)
    - Bloodborne Pathogen, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 328)
    - 77 Broadway, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 329)
    - Budget, 1998- 2004 (Box 12, Folder 330)
    - Caravan, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 331)
    - Controlled Substances, 1997- 2000 (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - Consultants, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 333)
    - Contingency Plan, 1994-2001 (Box 12, Folder 334)
    - Corporation, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 335)
    - DEP, 1999-2005 (Box 12, Folder 336)
    - DEP Power Plan, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 337)
    - Directors Meetings, 2003- 2004 (Box 12, Folder 338)
    - Directors Meetings, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 339)
    - Exit Signs, 2000- 2005 (Box 12, Folder 340)
    - EPA Self Audit, 2000- 2002 (Box 12, Folder 341)
    - EPA Self Audit, 2003- 2004 (Box 12, Folder 342)
    - EPA, 1999- 2001 (Box 12, Folder 343)
    - Asbestos, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 344)
    - Canavan, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 345)
    - EPA, 2000-2005 (Box 13, Folder 346)
    - EPA, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 347)
    - Freezer (EPH) Incident, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 348)
    - Ergonomics, 1998- 2002 (Box 13, Folder 349)
    - Golf Course, 1998- 1999 (Box 13, Folder 350)
    - Golf Course, 2000- 2001 (Box 13, Folder 351)
    - Grievances, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 352)
    - Hard Hats, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 353)
    - Infection Control, 1996- 2001 (Box 13, Folder 354)
    - Infection Control Work Group, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 355)
    - Incidents, 1995- 1998 (Box 13, Folder 356)
    - Incidents, 1999- 2003 (Box 13, Folder 357)
    - Injury Statistics, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 358)
    - Inspections, 1997- 1999 (Box 13, Folder 359)
    - Insurance, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 360)
    - Joint Health and Safety Committee, 1997- 2005 (Box 13, Folder 361)
    - KBT, 1997- 1998 (Box 13, Folder 362)
    - Lead, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 364)
    - Mavrogianis, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 365)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 1996 (Box 13, Folder 366)
    - Mood, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 367)
    - Mosquitoes, 2000- 2002 (Box 13, Folder 368)
    - Mouse Incidents, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 369)
    - Newsletters, 1995- 1999 (Box 13, Folder 370)
    - NRC License for Material, 1999- 2001 (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - OML, 2002- 2004 (Box 13, Folder 372)
    - OSHA, 1996, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 373)
    - Permits, 1995- 1997 (Box 13, Folder 374)
    - Personnel, 1995- 1997 (Box 13, Folder 375)
    - Praise, 1997- 2001 (Box 13, Folder 376)
    - Press, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 377)
    - Radiation Safety, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 378)
    - Radiation Safety, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 379)
    - Radioactive Waste, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 380)
    - Sabia Virus Incident, 1994- 1995 (Box 13, Folder 381 - 382)
    - Safety Bulletin, 1989- 2005 (Box 13, Folder 383)
    - Safety Committee, 1995- 20046 (Box 13, Folder 384 - 385)
    - Safety Responsibilities, 1996- 1997 (Box 13, Folder 386)
    - Select Agents, 2002- 2005 (Box 13, Folder 387)
    - Self Audit, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 388)
    - SEP'S, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 389)
    - Silver, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 390)
    - Stables, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 391)
    - Stockroom, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 392)
    - Strategic Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 393 - 394)
    - Sunshine Project, 2004 2006 (Box 14, Folder 396)
    - Surcharges, 1995- 2002 (Box 14, Folder 397)
    - Sustainability Project, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 398)
    - Table of Organization, 1993- 1996 (Box 14, Folder 399)
    - Training, 1996- 2000 (Box 14, Folder 400)
    - USDA, 1996- 1997 (Box 14, Folder 401)
    - Unions, 1996- 1997 (Box 14, Folder 402)
    - Unit Safety, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 403)
    - University Properties, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 404)
    - University Safety Committee Agenda, 1995- 1999 (Box 14, Folder 405)
    - University Safety Committee Agenda, 2000- 2005 (Box 14, Folder 406)
    - Radiation Safety, 1995- 2003 (Box 14, Folder 407 - 408)
    - Radiation Safety, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 409)
    - WPCA, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 410)
    - Waste Issues, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 412)
    - Whistleblower, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 413)
    - Workers Compensation, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 414)
    - YNHH, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 415)
    - YPB, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 416)
    - YPI, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 417)
    - YSM, 2002- 2003 (Box 14, Folder 418)
    - EPH, 1995- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 419 - 420)
  - EPH
    - ACCREDITATION, 1999- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 421)
    - AIDS CENTER, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 422)
    - APPOINTMENTS and PROMOTIONS, 2000- 2005 (Box 14, Folder 423)
    - BL 3, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 424)
    - BMS, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 425)
    - BUDGET, 1997- 2003 (Box 14, Folder 426)
    - CIRA, 1999- 2002 (Box 14, Folder 427)
    - CHEMISTRY, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 428)
    - COMMISSIONER OF PUBLIC HEALTH, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 429)
    - EPH CORRESPONDENCE, 1995- 2000 (Box 14, Folder 430)
    - DEAN APPOINTMENTS, 1995- 1998 (Box 14, Folder 432)
    - DEVELOPMENT, 1995- 1999 (Box 14, Folder 433)
    - FACILITIES, 1995 2001 (Box 14, Folder 434)
    - FACULTY ISSUES, 1995- 2003 (Box 14, Folder 436)
    - FACULTY TRACKS, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 437)
    - FINANCE, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 438)
    - GENERAL, 2002- 2003 (Box 14, Folder 439)
    - HEALTH MANAGEMENT, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 440)
    - LEGACY FOUNDATION, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 443)
    - MTV, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 444)
    - MANAGED CARE, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 445)
    - MASTERS DEGREE, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 446)
    - NEWSLETTERS, 1997- 2002 (Box 14, Folder 448)
    - NOBAY, 1995- 1998 (Box 14, Folder 449)
    - PRESS, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 451)
    - RANSOM, 1996 1999 (Box 14, Folder 452)
    - RICO-HESSE, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 453)
    - RUDDLE, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 454)
    - RUSSIA, 2003- 2004 (Box 14, Folder 455)